<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Trendy Cards</string>

    <string name="card_1_hyperlink"><a href="https://developer.android.com/get-started/overview">click here to learn more... </a></string>
    <string name="androidText">Android is a mobile operating system based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open-source software.\n\nIt’s designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets1. Android is developed by a consortium of developers known as the Open Handset Alliance, with its most widely used version primarily developed by Google.\n\nAndroid was unveiled in November 2007, with the first commercial Android device, the HTC Dream, being launched in September 2008.</string>

    <string name="card_2_hyperlink"><a href="https://www.ibm.com/topics/internet-of-things">click here to learn more... </a></string>
    <string name="IOTText">The Internet of Things (IoT) refers to a network of physical devices, vehicles, appliances, and other objects that are embedded with sensors, software, and network connectivity, allowing them to collect and share data.\n\nThese devices, also known as “smart objects”, can range from simple “smart home” devices like smart thermostats, to wearables like smartwatches and RFID-enabled clothing, to complex industrial machinery and transportation systems.</string>

    <string name="card_3_hyperlink"><a href="https://www.ibm.com/topics/blockchain">click here to learn more... </a></string>
    <string name="blockchainText">Blockchain technology is a decentralized, distributed ledger that stores the record of ownership of digital assets.\n\nIt’s a structure that stores transactional records, also known as the block, of the public in several databases, known as the “chain,” in a network connected through peer-to-peer nodes2. Typically, this storage is referred to as a ‘digital ledger’.\n\nBlockchain is a shared, immutable ledger that facilitates the process of recording transactions and tracking assets in a business network</string>

    <string name="card_4_hyperlink"><a href="https://cloud.google.com/learn/artificial-intelligence-vs-machine-learning">click here to learn more... </a></string>
    <string name="aimlText">Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) are two closely related fields that are revolutionizing the way we interact with technology.\n\nArtificial Intelligence (AI) is a broad field, which refers to the use of technologies to build machines and computers that have the ability to mimic cognitive functions associated with human intelligence, such as being able to see, understand, and respond to spoken or written language, analyze data, make recommendations, and more2. AI is often thought of as a system in itself, but it is a set of technologies implemented in a system to enable it to reason, learn, and act to solve a complex problem.\n\nMachine Learning (ML), on the other hand, is a subset of AI that automatically enables a machine or system to learn and improve from experience.</string>

    <string name="card_5_hyperlink"><a href="https://www.ibm.com/topics/quantum-computing#:~:text=What%20is%20quantum%20computing%3F%20Quantum%20computing%20uses%20specialized,supercomputers%20can%E2%80%99t%20solve%2C%20or%20can%E2%80%99t%20solve%20quickly%20enough.">click here to learn more... </a></string>
    <string name="quantumText">Quantum computing is an area of computing that uses quantum mechanics to process information. It leverages the principles of quantum theory, which explains the behavior of energy and material on the atomic and subatomic levels.\n\nQuantum computing uses subatomic particles, such as electrons or photons.\n\nA quantum computer is a computer that takes advantage of quantum mechanical phenomena1. On small scales, physical matter exhibits properties of both particles and waves, and quantum computing leverages this behavior, specifically quantum superposition and entanglement, using specialized hardware that supports the preparation and manipulation of quantum states.\n\nThe basic unit of information in quantum computing is the qubit, similar to the bit in traditional digital electronics.</string>

    <string name="card_6_hyperlink"><a href="https://aws.amazon.com/what-is/edge-computing/">click here to learn more... </a></string>
    <string name="edgeText">Edge computing is a distributed computing model that brings computation and data storage closer to the sources of data. This often makes applications faster.\n\nMore broadly, it refers to any design that pushes computation physically closer to a user, so as to reduce the latency compared to when an application runs on a single data center.\n\nEdge computing brings enterprise applications closer to data sources such as IoT devices or local edge servers1. This proximity to data at its source can deliver strong business benefits, including faster insights, improved response times, and better bandwidth availability.\n\nThe explosive growth and increasing computing power of IoT devices have resulted in unprecedented volumes of data.</string>
    <string name="buttonText">Go baby Go</string>
    <string name="myContentMSG">Hi, I am Sarthak Sharma, SDE @ Amazon and your tutor for today. Now this app will help you bout new technologies that are trendy these days. \n\nSo, without any furthure ado Let\'s get started.</string>

</resources>
